A Guide to the University of Virginia Division of Continuing Education, Miscellaneous Statistical Reports, 1932-1973
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
University of Virginia Division of Continuing Education, Miscellaneous Statistical Reports 1932-1973
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-16/1/3.771
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was an archival transfer from the Division of Continuing Education, 1977 July 11.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of miscellaneous statistical reports compiled by the Division of Continuing Education for various agencies including the State Council of Higher Education for Virginia, and the Office of Education, Dept. of Health, Education and Welfare.
Arrangement
The reports are arranged chronologically.
Contents List
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- AUEC NUEA Report, 1963-1973, 10 folders. (Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- HEW Forms, 1965-1966, 3 folders. (Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- Extension and Branch Enrollments, 1966 Fall (Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- Extension and Branch Registrations List Prepared for State Council of Higher Education, 1966 (Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- HEW Forms, 1966-1967, 2 folders. (Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Data- HEW Form re Library Resources and Facilities, 1966-1967 (Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- SCHEV Form, 1966-1967, 8 folders. (Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Folders- Report on Extension Enrollments, 1966-1967 (Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- HEW Forms; SCHEV Forms, 1967 Summer (Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- Schedule of Higher Education General Information Survey (HEW and SCHEV), 1967-1968 (Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Data- SCHEV Forms, 1967-1968, 2 folders. (Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- HEW Forms for Patrick Henry and Eastern Shore, 1968 Fall (Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- Schedule of Higher Education General Information Survey (HEW), 1968-1969 (Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- SCHEV Forms, 1968-1969 (Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- SCHEV Reports, 1968-1969 (Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- Work Copies of Report on Service Courses for Teachers, 1969 Fall (Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- Schedule of Higher Education General Information Survey (HEW and SCHEV), 1969-1970 (Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- HEW Forms, 1969-1970 (Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- National Education Association of the U.S. (Salary review questionnaire- Junior and Community Colleges), 1969-1970 (Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- SCHEV (Enrollment Projections for Patrick Henry and Eastern Shore), 1969-1970 (Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- SCHEV Forms, 1969-1970, 3 folders. (Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- SCHEV Forms, 1969-1970, 7 folders. (Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- Instruction Sheets, Code Numbers and Correspondence related to HEW and SCHEV Forms, 1969-1970 (Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- Non-Duplicating Student Enrollment, 1969-1970 (Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- HEW Reports, 1970 (Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports-SCHEV Forms, 1970 (Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- Schedule of Higher Education General Information Survey (HEW), 1970-1971 (Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- SCHEV Forms, 1970-1971, 2 folders. (Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- SCHEV Forms, 1970-1971, 3 folders. (Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- Code Numbers, Instruction Sheets and Related Correspondence for SHEV Forms, 1970-1971 (Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- HEW Forms; SCHEV: Statistics, 1970-1971 (Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- Data Processing Non-Duplicating Student Enrollment, 1970-1971 (Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- Data and Unnumbered Reports Prepared by Extension Instruction, 1970-1971, 2 folders. (Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- Southern Association of Colleges and Schools, 1971 (Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- Virginia Advisory Legislative Council 1971 (Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- HEW Forms, 1971-1972, 2 folders. (Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- Work Sheets, Information used in preparing OE Forms, 1971-1972 (Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- NUEA Survey, Marajuana and Drug Education Programs, 1971-1972 (Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- SCHEV Forms, 1971-1972, 3 folders. (Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- Surveys and Questionnaires, 1971-1972 (Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- SCHEV, 1974-1976 (Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous Statistical Reports- Blank Forms, n.d. (Folder 7)